do this this is like a loving this is the loving the loving segment we love each other so much it's
so good to see you it like makes me actually brings me joy and lifts my spirits to see to see
your face oh same sis i wanted to ask i mean you've been to cuba um and you know i i'm wondering
if you could share with us a little bit more about the most memorable moments like what are some of
the most impactful moments some of the lessons that you that you could talk to us about from from
having visited cuba i mean it's so hard to like narrow down but i guess i have to because cuba
is such an amazing place but you can also see the impact of the blockade so immediately when you're
there because it's kind of like there's a part of it that feels like going back in time and it feels
kind of cool you're like oh these cars are so like old and vintage but it's actually right because they
can't like import new cars so they have to find ways to make things work so there's like a
beautiful almost stuck in time element to cuba